Historical Materials Collection UA136
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Photographs, 1819 -- 2009; UA136.002; 4.6 Linear Feet; 1 Artifact(s); 1412 Digital Object(s)
  - Class Day, students gathered in front of Ballou Hall, 1910; UA136.002.DO.03982; Unknown (Box Shared 19)
    12 x 15
    People; Men; Events; Class Day; photographic print
  - Student Army Taining Corps, Officers, 1918; UA136.002.DO.03983; Notman (Box Shared 19)
    16 x 10
    World War, 1914-1918; Men; People; photographic print; Student Army Training Corps
  - Crane Theological School, 1912; UA136.002.DO.03984; Unknown (Box Shared 19)
    9 x 13
    Men; Students; People; photographic print; Crane Theological School
  - View of Hill from Powderhouse Boulevard, 1910; UA136.002.DO.03985; Unknown (Box Shared 19)
    20 x 10
  - Glee club, 1908; UA136.002.DO.03986; E. Chickering and Co. (Box Shared 66)
    14 x 17
    Men; Students; People; Music and musical performances; Student activities; photographic print; Glee Club
  - Group of students, 1910; UA136.002.DO.03987; Unknown (Box Shared 66)
    14 x 16
    Students; Men; People; photographic print
  - Men gathered at dinner, Theta Delta Chi fraternity house, 1900; UA136.002.DO.03991; Unknown (Box Shared 66)
    Men; Students; Fraternities; photographic print; Theta Delta Chi
  - Tufts College Centennial Pageant, June, 1952; UA136.002.DO.03993; Hotel Photo Service (Box Shared 66)
    20 x 8
    Students; Events; People; Music and musical performances; photographic print
  - Tufts Centennial Celebration, 1952; UA136.002.DO.04006; Unknown (Box Shared 66)
    Celebrations; People; Events; photographic print
  - Students in "Old Fortunatics," June, 1906; UA136.002.DO.04007; Unknown (Box Shared 66)
    Drama; Student activities; People; photographic print
  - Students in "Old Fortunatics," June, 1906; UA136.002.DO.04008; Stebbins, N.L. (Box Shared 66)
  - Students in "Old Fortunatics," June, 1906; UA136.002.DO.04009; Gale, Dr. Howard Charles (Box Shared 66)
  - John Thelan and Howard Charles Gale in "Old Fortunatics," June, 1906; UA136.002.DO.04010; Gale, Dr. Howard Charles (Box Shared 66)
    Drama; Student activities; People; photographic print; Thelan, John; Gale, Howard Charles
  - Caricature of Professor Russell Carpenter, 1942; UA136.002.DO.04011; Unknown
    Attached note reads, "For Bud whose influence on me and on hundreds of his other students has been greater than he knows. For Bud who made me get those diagrams on paper. From his friend and admirer, Bob"
    Carpenter, Russell L.
  - Sudents in production of "The College Hero," n.d., UA136.002.DO.04012; Unknown (Box Shared 66)
    15 x 18
    Drama; Student activities; People; Theater; photographic print
  - Richard Cochran (E1934), Donald Cochrane (E1933), and Arthur Cochran (E1932, G1933), 1935; UA136.002.DO.04021; Dwight Davis Photo (Box Shared 67)
    People; Men; photographic print; Cochran, Richard; Cochrane, Donald; Cochran, Arthur
  - Professor William R. Shipman, 1875; UA136.002.DO.04046; Unknown (Box Shared 18)
    People; Faculty; Deans; photographic print; Shipman, William R.; Dept. of English; Phi Beta Kappa
  - Professor William R. Shipman, 1880; UA136.002.DO.04047; Hardy (Box Shared 18)
  - Professor William R. Shipman, 1895; UA136.002.DO.04048; Hastings (Box Shared 18)
  - Professor William R. Shipman, 1870; UA136.002.DO.04049; Unknown (Box Shared 18)
  - Professor William R. Shipman, 1895; UA136.002.DO.04050; Unknown (Box Shared 18)
  - Professor William R. Shipman, 1870; UA136.002.DO.04051; Unknown (Box Shared 121)
    8.5x6
  - Professor William R. Shipman, 1895; UA136.002.DO.04052; Smith, G. Waldon (Box Shared 18)
  - Professor William R. Shipman, 1891; UA136.002.DO.04053; Davis and Dow (Box Shared 18)
  - Professor William R. Shipman, 1887; UA136.002.DO.04054; Ritz (Box Shared 18)
  - Professor William R. Shipman, 1880; UA136.002.DO.04055; Clark, W. Loring (Box Shared 18)
  - Professor William R. Shipman, 1880; UA136.002.DO.04056; Unknown (Box Shared 121)
    9x7
  - Professor William R. Shipman, 1885; UA136.002.DO.04057; Unknown (Box Shared 121)
    photo is a copy of the original print (location unknown)
  - Professor William R. Shipman, 1895; UA136.002.DO.04058; Chickering, Elmer (Box Shared 121)
    9x6
  - Dean Lee Sullivan McCollester, 1885; UA136.002.DO.04059; Unknown (Box Shared 18)
    photograph is oval-shaped
    People; Faculty; Deans; photographic print; McCollester, Lee Sullivan; Divinity School
  - Frederick Crosby Hodgdon, 1894; UA136.002.DO.04067; Unknown
    cartes de visite
    People; Students; Alumni and alumnae; Hodgdon, Frederick C.; Board of Trustees
  - Jane and Frederick C. Hodgdon at their home, 4 Gramercy Park, NY, 1935; UA136.002.DO.04068; Unknown (Box Shared 122)
    Date is approximate but before 1940/1941 when portrait by Cornelis Janssens and a T'ang horse were on and above mantel piece.
    People; Alumni and alumnae; photographic print; Hodgdon, Frederick C.; Hodgdon, Jane; Board of Trustees
  - Sol Gittleman, Associate Professor and Chairman of the Department of German, UA136.002.DO.04117; Unknown (Box Shared 122)
    People; Faculty; photographic print; Gittleman, Sol, 1934-
  - Sol Gittleman speaking to alumni/ae in classroom, UA136.002.DO.04118; Unknown (Box Shared 122)
    People; Alumni and alumnae; Faculty; photographic print; Gittleman, Sol, 1934-
  - Sol Gittleman, UA136.002.DO.04119; Unknown (Box Shared 18)
    5x6
  - Sol Gittleman speaking with Warren A. Little under tree. n.d., UA136.002.DO.04120; Unknown (Box Shared 122)
    man on left identified on back of print as Warren A. Little 71
    People; Faculty; Alumni and alumnae; photographic print; Gittleman, Sol, 1934-; Little, Warren A.
  - Associate Professor Sol Gittleman, German, UA136.002.DO.04121; Unknown (Box Shared 18)
  - Professor Sol Gittleman, German, UA136.002.DO.04122; Unknown (Box Shared 18)
    7x5
  - Sol Gittleman, 1970; UA136.002.DO.04123; Unknown (Box Shared 18)
    identified as "6" on contact sheet (upper lefthand image)
  - Sol Gittleman, 1970; UA136.002.DO.04124; Unknown (Box Shared 18)
    identified as "9" on contact sheet (upper righthand image)
  - Sol Gittleman, 1970; UA136.002.DO.04125; Unknown (Box Shared 18)
    identified as "8" on contact sheet (middle right image).
  - Vannevar Bush at presentation of Hosea Ballou Medal, Waldorf-Astoria Hotel, NYC, to Herbert Hoover, 1959; UA136.002.DO.04126; Unknown (Box Shared 122)
    People; Alumni and alumnae; photographic print; Bush, Vannevar
  - Vannevar Bush in his twenties, 1915; UA136.002.DO.04127; Unknown (Box Shared 122)
    People; Faculty; Alumni and alumnae; photographic print; Bush, Vannevar
  - Vannevar Bush, UA136.002.DO.04128; Unknown (Box Shared 122)
    color photo
  - Deborah Nutter, 1998; UA136.002.DO.04129; Unknown (Box Shared 18)
    People; College administrators; Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy, records; photographic print; Nutter, Deborah; Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy
  - Vannevar Bush receiving Alumni Distinguished Service Award, 1947; UA136.002.DO.04131; Unknown (Box Shared 122)
    People; Alumni and alumnae; photographic print; Reynolds, Joel W.; Bush, Vannevar
  - Vannevar Bush caricature, 1962; UA136.002.DO.04132; Unknown (Box Shared 122)
    glossy image of drawing
  - Profile of Vannevar Bush in academic regalia, 1958; UA136.002.DO.04133; Unknown (Box Shared 123)
  - Vannevar Bush leaning on podum, 1963; UA136.002.DO.04134; Unknown (Box Shared 18)
  - Vannevar Bush at desk, UA136.002.DO.04135; Unknown (Box Shared 18)
    "M.I.T. photo" written on verso
  - Vannevar Bush at desk, close-range, UA136.002.DO.04136; Unknown (Box Shared 18)
  - Vannevar Bush, 1962; UA136.002.DO.04137; Hessler Studio (Box Shared 123)
    Alumni and alumnae; Portraits; College trustees; photographic print; Bush, Vannevar
  - Vannevar Bush, 1961; UA136.002.DO.04138; Unknown (Box Shared 18)
    75. 8 x 10 copy housed in vertical file cabinet.
    Alumni and alumnae; College trustees; photographic print; Bush, Vannevar
  - Dr. Ashley Campbell, Dean of Engineering School, and Dr. Vannevar Bush of MIT, 1967-03-01; UA136.002.DO.04139; Unknown (Box Shared 18)
    Duplicate in veritcal file cabinet.
    College administrators; Alumni and alumnae; College trustees; photographic print; Bush, Vannevar; Campbell, Ashley S., 1918-
  - Vannevar Bush, 1925; UA136.002.DO.04140; Unknown (Box Shared 18)
    75. This date is approximate.
    College trustees; Alumni and alumnae; Portraits; photographic print; Bush, Vannevar
  - Vannevar Bush in academic regalia, 1960; UA136.002.DO.04141; Unknown (Box Shared 18)
    College trustees; Alumni and alumnae; photographic print; Bush, Vannevar
  - Vannevar Bush speaking on panel, 1963; UA136.002.DO.04142; Unknown (Box Shared 123)
  - Vannevar Bush, seated portrait, 1955; UA136.002.DO.04143; Unknown (Box Shared 123)
    color photo.
  - Rugby team, 1974; UA136.002.DO.04144; Unknown (Box Shared 18)
    People; Students; Athletics; Rugby; photographic print
  - Rosalyn Do, secretary of the Class of 1989, adjusts the hat of her good fried Mark Kizior, class treasurer, UA136.002.DO.04196; Unknown (Box Shared 18)
    Commencement; Students; photographic print; Do, Rosalyn; Kizior, Mark
  - Medical School graduation, 1989; UA136.002.DO.04197; Unknown (Box Shared 18)
    Commencement; Students; photographic print; Tufts Medical School
  - Class president James Kostas, speaking at graduation, UA136.002.DO.04198; Unknown (Box Shared 18)
    Commencement; Students; Speeches; photographic print; Kostas, James
  - Shy Fire, Senior Week, 1989; UA136.002.DO.04199; O'Connell, Bill (Box Shared 123)
    Students; Music and musical performances; photographic print
  - Students playing volleyball, Senior Week, 1989; UA136.002.DO.04200; O'Connell, Bill (Box Shared 123)
    Students; Events; Volleyball; photographic print
  - Kristen Hick, Kimberly Barrie, and Amy Kemp, Senior Week, 1989; UA136.002.DO.04201 (Box Shared 123)
    Events; Students; Hick, Kristen; Barrie, Kimberly; Kemp, Amy
  - Postcard of the bubble, Packard Hall and East Hall, 1910; UA136.002.DO.04271; Unknown (Box Shared 20)
    Picture postcards; Buildings; photographic print
  - Classics and Music Professor Roslyn Brogue Henning, 1970; UA136.002.DO.04391; Unknown (Box Shared 20)
    Photo from vertical file.
    People; Women; Professors; photographic print; Henning, Roslyn Brogue; Dept. of Classics; Department of Music
  - Roslyn Brogue Henning at harpsichord, 1970; UA136.002.DO.04392; Unknown (Box Shared 68)
  - Thomas S. Knight, Tufts Trustee, 1963; UA136.002.DO.04393; Bachrach (Box Shared 68)
    Portraits; photographic print; Knight, Thomas S.; Board of Trustees
  - Hall of Flags, Cabot Intercultural Center, October, 1988; UA136.002.DO.04410; Unknown (Box Shared 20)
    People; Buildings; Interior views; Students; photographic print; Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy
  - Ballou Hall, 1865; UA136.002.DO.04435; Unknown (Box Shared 37)
    There is also a 5x7 stereograph with the same UI number
    Buildings; Exterior views; photographic print
  - Thomas S. Knight, 1903; UA136.002.DO.04449; Unknown (Box Shared 69)
    Students; photographic print; Knight, Thomas S.; Board of Trustees
  - Thomas S. Knight, 1950; UA136.002.DO.04450; Unknown (Box Shared 69)
  - Dr. Vivian Pinn, 1975; UA136.002.DO.04627; Unknown (Box Shared 20)
    This date is approximate. Photo from vertical file.
    photographic print; Pinn, Vivian; School of Medicine
  - Magic Circle Theater production of "Alice in Wonderland,", 1961; UA136.002.DO.04639; Duette Photographers (Box Shared 37)
    People; Actors; Plays; photographic print; Magic Circle Theater
  - Magic Circle Theater production of "Emperor Pix,", 1961; UA136.002.DO.04640; Duette Photographers (Box Shared 37)
    People; Actors; Plays; photographic print; Magic Circle Theater; Tufts University
  - Students walking in front of West Hall, 1964; UA136.002.DO.04661; Unknown (Box Shared 124)
    Buildings; Dormitories; Trees; Students; Automobiles; photographic print; Tufts University
  - Student walking in front of West Hall, 1975; UA136.002.DO.04662; Unknown (Box Shared 124)
    Buildings; Dormitories; Students; photographic print; Tufts University
  - West Hall and Old Campus Reservoir, 1890; UA136.002.DO.04663; Unknown (Box Shared 20)
    5x4
    Buildings; Dormitories; Reservoirs; photographic print; Tufts University
  - Workers painting West Hall, 1960; UA136.002.DO.04664; Cohen, Peter (Box Shared 124)
    Buildings; Dormitories; Workers; Scaffolds; photographic print; Tufts University
  - Student walking in front of East Hall, 1974; UA136.002.DO.04666; McLaren, Lynn (Box Shared 124)
  - Students lounging in front of East Hall, 1870; UA136.002.DO.04667; Unknown (Box Shared 124)
  - Students congregating in front of East Hall, 1870; UA136.002.DO.04669; Unknown (Box Shared 124)
    8x7
  - East Hall, 1890; UA136.002.DO.04670; Unknown (Box Shared 124)
    Buildings; Dormitories; photographic print; Tufts University
  - Students gazing out of the windows of East Hall, 1887; UA136.002.DO.04671; Unknown (Box Shared 124)
  - Men in front of Packard Hall, 1870; UA136.002.DO.04672; Unknown (Box Shared 20)
    Buildings; Dormitories; People; photographic print; Tufts University
  - Students in front of Packard Hall, 1960; UA136.002.DO.04673; Unknown (Box Shared 124)
  - Packard Hall and barn, 1860; UA136.002.DO.04674; Unknown (Box Shared 124)
    Buildings; Dormitories; Barns; photographic print; Tufts University
  - Rear of Packard Hall, 1940; UA136.002.DO.04675; Unknown (Box Shared 20)
    4x3
    Buildings; Dormitories; Windows; photographic print; Tufts University
  - Daniel Pratt delivering a lecture in front of Packard Hall, May, 1885; UA136.002.DO.04676; Unknown (Box Shared 125)
    Buildings; Dormitories; Lectures or lecturing; Students; photographic print; Pratt, Daniel; Tufts University
  - Students in front of Ballou Hall, 1977; UA136.002.DO.04677; McLaren, Lynn (Box Shared 125)
    Buildings; Academic; Administrative; Students; photographic print; Tufts University
  - Student in front of east side of Ballou Hall, 1960; UA136.002.DO.04679; Unknown (Box Shared 125)
  - Students in front of Ballou Hall, 1947; UA136.002.DO.04682; Unknown (Box Shared 125)
    Buildings; Administrative; Academic; Automobiles; photographic print; Tufts University
  - Rededication of Ballou Hall, 9 June, 1956; UA136.002.DO.04687; Unknown (Box Shared 125)
    Buildings; Ceremonies; Interior views; People; photographic print; Grant, Arnold; Hill, Robert W.; Anderson, Arthur J.; Wessell, Nils Yngve; Cain, Walker; Mark, Rev. John Nicol; Tufts University
  - President Wessell addresses group in Coolidge Room, 1956; UA136.002.DO.04689; Duette (Box Shared 125)
    Lectures or lecturing; Interior views; People; College presidents; photographic print; Wessell, Nils Yngve; Tufts University
  - Sketch of Tuft's College featuring Ballou Hall, Packard Hall, and Ballou House, 1870; UA136.002.DO.04690; Unknown (Box Shared 125)
    Buildings; Illustrations; Sketches; Houses; photographic print; Tufts University
  - View of Downhill dormitories, 1970; UA136.002.DO.04691; McLaren, Lynn (Box data_value_missing_65daf95ecc907f274f1e411f374fe213)
    Buildings; Dormitories; Exterior views; photographic print; Tufts University
  - Unidentified students sitting on the steps of Stratton Hall, 1959; UA136.002.DO.04692; Duette Photographers (Box data_value_missing_65daf95ecc907f274f1e411f374fe213)
    Buildings; Dormitories; Exterior views; Students; People; photographic print; Tufts University
  - Stratton Hall, 1970; UA136.002.DO.04693; Unknown (Box Shared 21)
    Buildings; Dormitories; Exterior views; Students; photographic print; Tufts University
  - Construction of Stratton Hall, 3 October, 1927; UA136.002.DO.04694; Unknown (Box Shared 21)
    tear in upper-right corner; marking in lower-left corner
    Buildings; Dormitories; Exterior views; Construction; Scaffolds; Workers; photographic print; Tufts University
  - View of room 24 in Stratton Hall, 1928; UA136.002.DO.04695; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_65daf95ecc907f274f1e411f374fe213)
    Buildings; Dormitories; Rooms; Interior views; photographic print; Tufts University
  - Unidentified couple admiring the exterior of Haskell Hall, 1966; UA136.002.DO.04696; Duette Photographers (Box data_value_missing_65daf95ecc907f274f1e411f374fe213)
    Buildings; Dormitories; Exterior views; People; photographic print; Tufts University
  - Student in window of Haskell Hall, 1970; UA136.002.DO.04697; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_65daf95ecc907f274f1e411f374fe213)
  - Tilton Hall lounge, 1970; UA136.002.DO.04698; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_65daf95ecc907f274f1e411f374fe213)
    marking on top, left, and bottom sides
    Buildings; Dormitories; Interior views; photographic print; Tufts University
  - Wren Hall lounge, 1970; UA136.002.DO.04699; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_65daf95ecc907f274f1e411f374fe213)
    Buildings; Interior views; Dormitories; photographic print
  - Ten student suite, floorplan, 1970; UA136.002.DO.04700; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_65daf95ecc907f274f1e411f374fe213)
    Builing possibly identified as Wren Hall. This date is approximate.
    Plan views; Dormitories; photographic print
  - Wren hall construction, 1964; UA136.002.DO.04701; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_65daf95ecc907f274f1e411f374fe213)
  - Students playing pinball and ping pong in lounge in Eaton Hall, 1975; UA136.002.DO.04702; Mackson, Lisa (Box data_value_missing_65daf95ecc907f274f1e411f374fe213)
    Students; Games; photographic print
  - Students relaxing in lounge in Eaton Hall, 1980; UA136.002.DO.04703; Mackson, Lisa (Box data_value_missing_65daf95ecc907f274f1e411f374fe213)
  - Student lounge in Eaton Hall before conversion to computer center, 1980; UA136.002.DO.04704; Wood, Richard (Box data_value_missing_65daf95ecc907f274f1e411f374fe213)
  - Hall of Flags, Cabot Intercultural Center, 1992; UA136.002.DO.04877; Cranna, Greig (Box Shared 21)
    People; Buildings; Interior views; Flags; photographic print; Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy
  - Hall of Flags, Cabot Intercultural Center, 1992; UA136.002.DO.04878; Cranna, Greig (Box Shared 21)
  - Mugar Hall in winter, 1980; UA136.002.DO.04879; Unknown (Box Shared 21)
    Buildings; Exterior views; photographic print; Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy
  - Hall of Flags, Cabot Intercultural Center, 1992; UA136.002.DO.04880; Cranna, Greig (Box Shared 21)
    People; Interior views; photographic print; Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy
  - Goddard Hall, 1955; UA136.002.DO.04881; Unknown (Box Shared 22)
    Buildings; Exterior views; People; photographic print; Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy
  - Mugar Hall, 1980; UA136.002.DO.04882; Unknown (Box Shared 22)
  - Aerial view of Blakeley Hall, 1985; UA136.002.DO.04888; Unknown (Box Shared 22)
    Buildings; Aerial views; photographic print; Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy
  - Cabot Intercultural Center, 7th floor patio, 1987; UA136.002.DO.04889; Unknown (Box Shared 22)
    Buildings; People; photographic print; Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy
  - Mugar Hall, 1984; UA136.002.DO.04890; Macone, Allessandro (Box Shared 22)
  - Goddard Chapel and Ballou Hall, 1900; UA136.002.DO.05029; Metropolitan Water Works (Box data_value_missing_d3140b2bed06b92bcbd96b6521dc5b1e)
    Chapels; Buildings; Flags; glass negative; Tufts University
  - Isaac Royall House, Medford, 1900; UA136.002.DO.05030; Metropolitan Water Works (Box data_value_missing_d3140b2bed06b92bcbd96b6521dc5b1e)
    Buildings; Houses; glass negative
  - Isaac Royall House, Medford, 1900; UA136.002.DO.05031; Metropolitan Water Works (Box data_value_missing_d3140b2bed06b92bcbd96b6521dc5b1e)
  - Powder House, Somerville, 1900; UA136.002.DO.05032; Metropolitan Water Works (Box data_value_missing_d3140b2bed06b92bcbd96b6521dc5b1e)
    plate is broken in upper-right corner
    Buildings; glass negative
  - Senator Daniel Patrick Moynihan delivering a speech at the Fletcher School, 1983-04-21; UA136.002.DO.05033; Unknown (Box Shared 71)
    People; Politician; Speeches; photographic print; Moynihan, Daniel Patrick; Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy
  - Senator Daniel Patrick Moynihan, 1977; UA136.002.DO.05034; Unknown (Box Shared 71)
  - Senator Daniel Patrick Moynihan with public at Mugar Hall reception, 1977; UA136.002.DO.05035; Unknown (Box Shared 71)
    People; Politician; Reception; photographic print; Moynihan, Daniel Patrick; Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy
  - Senator Daniel Patrick Moynihan speaking, 1977; UA136.002.DO.05036; Unknown (Box Shared 71)
  - AMRAD Corporation, 1925; UA136.002.DO.05037; Unknown (Box Shared 21)
    5x3
    Buildings; photographic print; AMRAD
  - Jackson College dancers rehearsing, (l to r) Jean Glancy, J1953, Anne Jenkins, A1952, Loris Lakso, J1952, Diana Howard, J1953, Mary Ellen Fitzgerald, J1953, 1951; UA136.002.DO.05055; Unknown (Box Shared 71)
    People; Students; Women; Dances and Dancing; photographic print; Glancy, Jean; Jenkins, Anne; Lakso, Loris; Howard, Diana; Fitzgerald, Mary Ellen; Jackson College
  - Jackson College students in laboratory, 1942; UA136.002.DO.05056; Unknown (Box Shared 21)
    People; Students; Women; Laboratories; photographic print; Jackson College
  - Jackson College student, 1969; UA136.002.DO.05057; Duette Photographers (Box Shared 21)
    People; Students; Women; photographic print; Jackson College
  - John Vannevar, R1880, H1904, UA136.002.DO.05060; Clark, W. Loring (Box Shared 21)
    People; Men; photographic print; Vannevar, John
  - Charles Rockwell Jenney, H1922, 1890; UA136.002.DO.05061; Hardy (Box Shared 21)
    People; Men; photographic print; Jenney, Charles Rockwell
  - Albert C. White, R1880, UA136.002.DO.05062; Clark, W. Loring (Box Shared 21)
    People; Men; photographic print; White, Albert C.
  - G. D. Barnes, R1877, 1880; UA136.002.DO.05064; Clark, W. Loring (Box Shared 21)
    People; Men; photographic print; Barnes, G. D.
  - James Harcourt West, R1885, UA136.002.DO.05065; Clark, W. Loring (Box Shared 21)
    People; Men; photographic print; West, James Harcourt
  - Charles Edward Nash, R1878, H1891, 1890; UA136.002.DO.05066; Clark, W. Loring (Box Shared 21)
    People; Men; photographic print; Nash, Charles Edward
  - Kellerman, Robert S., R1879, 1877; UA136.002.DO.05067; Clark, W. Loring (Box Shared 21)
    People; Men; photographic print; Kellerman, Robert S.
  - Harrison Spofford Whitman, R1877, H1899, 1880; UA136.002.DO.05068; Clark, W. Loring (Box Shared 21)
    People; Men; photographic print; Whitman, Harrison Spofford
  - Halligan Hall and Cousens Gymnasium, February 9, 1932; UA136.002.DO.05069; Andover Press (Box Shared 71)
  - Birthplace of Hosea Ballou 2nd, Guilford, Vermont, 1971; UA136.002.DO.05074; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
    Gift of Peter Knost
    Buildings; Exterior views; slide (photograph); Ballou, Hosea, 2d
  - Stratton Lounge ready for Junior Dinner Dance, Marie Hedin, J1968, Donald Dehollis, A1967, Mattie Robertson, J1968, Harry Gustafson, A1968, 1966; UA136.002.DO.05126; Unknown (Box Shared 21)
    People; Students; Dances and Dancing; photographic print; Hedin, Marie; Dehollis, Donald; Gustafson, Mattie Robertson; Gustafson, Harry
  - Stratton Hall's Christmas Party, Judy Sutton (with headband), Suzanne Gould, J1968, Rene Bejosa, Mareen McGonigle, Alice Beake (with nightcap), Leslie Bell Wharton, J1968, Judith Breakstone, J1968, December, 1964; UA136.002.DO.05127; Unknown (Box Shared 21)
    People; Students; Holidays; Parties; photographic print; Sutton, Judy; Gould, Suzanne; Bejosa, Rene; McGonigle, Maureen; Beake, Alice; Wharton, Leslie Bell; Breakstone, Judith